question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals", "question": "A slug&rsquo;s blood is green.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
         "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
         "question": "Israel is 7 hours ahead of New York.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
         "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
